<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Readfiles on Fooston</title>
    <link>https://fooston.com/readfiles/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Readfiles on Fooston</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="https://fooston.com/readfiles/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://fooston.com/readfiles/readme/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fooston.com/readfiles/readme/</guid>
      <description>readdirs Directory for Reusable Content Files in this directory are:
 Used in more than one place within the Hugo docs Used in Examples of readdir (i.e. in local file templates)  These files are called using the readfile shortcode (source).
You can call this shortcode in the docs as follows:
{{% readfile file=&amp;ldquo;/path/to/file.txt&amp;rdquo; markdown=&amp;ldquo;true&amp;rdquo; %}}
markdown=&amp;quot;true&amp;quot; is optional (default = &amp;quot;false&amp;quot;) and parses the string through the Blackfriday renderer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://fooston.com/readfiles/bfconfig/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fooston.com/readfiles/bfconfig/</guid>
      <description>Blackfriday Options  taskLists default: true
Blackfriday flag: Purpose: false turns off GitHub-style automatic task/TODO list generation. smartypants default: true Blackfriday flag: HTML_USE_SMARTYPANTS Purpose: false disables smart punctuation substitutions, including smart quotes, smart dashes, smart fractions, etc. If true, it may be fine-tuned with the angledQuotes, fractions, smartDashes, and latexDashes flags (see below). smartypantsQuotesNBSP default: false Blackfriday flag: HTML_SMARTYPANTS_QUOTES_NBSP Purpose: true enables French style Guillemets with non-breaking space inside the quotes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://fooston.com/readfiles/dateformatting/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fooston.com/readfiles/dateformatting/</guid>
      <description>Go templates format your dates according to a single reference time:
Mon Jan 2 15:04:05 MST 2006  You can think of MST as 07, thus making the reference format string a sequence of numbers. The following is taken directly from the Go docs:
Jan 2 15:04:05 2006 MST 1 2 3 4 5 6 -7  Hugo Date Templating Reference Each of the following examples show the reference formatting string followed by the string Hugo will output in your HTML.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://fooston.com/readfiles/menuvars/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fooston.com/readfiles/menuvars/</guid>
      <description> .URL string .Name string .Menu string .Identifier string .Pre template.HTML .Post template.HTML .Weight int .Parent string .Children Menu  Note that menus also have the following functions available as well:
 .HasChildren boolean  Additionally, there are some relevant functions available to menus on a page:
 .IsMenuCurrent (menu string, menuEntry *MenuEntry ) boolean .HasMenuCurrent (menu string, menuEntry *MenuEntry) boolean  </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>