<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Foosball in Houston, TX on Fooston</title>
    <link>https://fooston.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Foosball in Houston, TX on Fooston</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2017 12:00:00 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://fooston.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Materials and Hardware</title>
      <link>https://fooston.com/foosball-rules/materials-and-hardware/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Sep 2017 16:22:04 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fooston.com/foosball-rules/materials-and-hardware/</guid>
      <description>Table  The Official tables are voted by ITSF General Assembly. This choice of table can be modified according to the agreements between the ITSF and manufacturers and partners.   The organizers must provide competitive equipment (sandpapered players, clean and straight bars).   In no cases may the surface of the table be sandpapered, and doing so will be penalized by exclusion of the tournament and reimbursement of the surface.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>31. Side Events</title>
      <link>https://fooston.com/foosball-rules/side-events/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Sep 2017 22:10:48 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fooston.com/foosball-rules/side-events/</guid>
      <description>Goalie War Goalie War is a singles specialty event where the three-man and five-man rods are lifted and the player shoot against each other from the goalie positions.
The Serve  To begin play, the ball must be moved from one player figure to another but may not be directly advanced from the second figure. After contacting the second player figure, the ball may be directly advanced by any other player figure.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>30. Tournament Director</title>
      <link>https://fooston.com/foosball-rules/tournament-director/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Sep 2017 22:09:03 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fooston.com/foosball-rules/tournament-director/</guid>
      <description>The administration of tournament play shall be the responsibility of the Tournament Director. This includes making the draws, scheduling the events, timing matches, etc. The decision of the Tournament Director in such matters is final.
30.1 All matters pertaining to rules of play (appointing Referees, handling appeals, etc.) shall be the responsibility of the Head Official. The Tournament Director is responsible for appointing the Head Official.
30.2 In every sanctioned ITSF tournament the Tournament Director is subordinate to the ITSF Sport Commission.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>29. Dress Code</title>
      <link>https://fooston.com/foosball-rules/dress-code/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Sep 2017 22:05:10 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fooston.com/foosball-rules/dress-code/</guid>
      <description>Players who wish to compete in an ITSF sanctioned event must wear proper sporting attire and are expected to uphold the highest level of personal and professional appearance. Enforcement of the dress code is the responsibility of the Tournament Director, the Head Official and/or a member of the ITSF Sporting Commission.
29.1 Acceptable sporting attire consists of warm-up jackets and pants, athletic shirts, sport tee shirts, polo shirts, athletic shorts, and athletic shoes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>28. Rules Decisions and Appeals</title>
      <link>https://fooston.com/foosball-rules/rules-decisions-and-appeals/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Sep 2017 22:02:38 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fooston.com/foosball-rules/rules-decisions-and-appeals/</guid>
      <description>If a controversy involves a question of judgment and a Referee was present at the time the events in question transpired, his decision is final and no appeal may be made. If the controversy involved an interpretation of the rules, or a Referee was not present at the time the events in question transpired, the Referee shall make the most equitable decision possible under the circumstances. Decisions of this nature may be appealed, but it must be done immediately in the manner prescribed below.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>27. Technical Fouls</title>
      <link>https://fooston.com/foosball-rules/technical-fouls/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Sep 2017 21:57:31 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fooston.com/foosball-rules/technical-fouls/</guid>
      <description>If, in the judgment of an authorized tournament Referee, either team competing in a match is at any time in flagrant or intentional violation of these rules of play, a technical foul may be called on the offending team.
27.1 When a technical foul is called, play shall stop and the opponent will be awarded the ball on the three-man rod. Only the player shooting and the player blocking are allowed to stay at the table.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>26. Recalls and Forfeiture</title>
      <link>https://fooston.com/foosball-rules/recalls-and-forfeiture/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Sep 2017 21:55:48 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fooston.com/foosball-rules/recalls-and-forfeiture/</guid>
      <description>Once a match has been called, both teams should report immediately to the designated table. If a team has not reported to the table within three minutes, they should be recalled. A team, upon being recalled, must report immediately to the table in order to stop the forfeiture process.
26.1 A recall is made every three minutes. Penalty for third and subsequent recalls is forfeiture of each game until the match is over.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>25. Delay of Game</title>
      <link>https://fooston.com/foosball-rules/delay-of-game/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Sep 2017 21:53:36 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fooston.com/foosball-rules/delay-of-game/</guid>
      <description>Play shall be continuous, except during time outs. Continuous shall be defined as no more than 5 seconds duration between a ball scored and the beginning of the ready protocol unless otherwise modified for televised matches. In Multi-table events, players have 5 seconds to assume their positions when switching between tables. A delay of game penalty may only be called by a Referee.
25.1 After a team is charged with delay of game play shall resume in at most 10 seconds.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>24. Time of Possession</title>
      <link>https://fooston.com/foosball-rules/time-of-possession/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Sep 2017 21:51:39 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fooston.com/foosball-rules/time-of-possession/</guid>
      <description>Possession of the ball shall be limited to 10 seconds on the five-man rod and 15 seconds on all other rods. A player is considered to be in possession of the ball the moment it is within reach of a player figure. Both goalie rods are considered one rod of possession.
24.1 A ball is considered to have advanced once it leaves the current rod of possession whether it goes forward or backwards.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>23. Passing</title>
      <link>https://fooston.com/foosball-rules/passing/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Sep 2017 21:46:15 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fooston.com/foosball-rules/passing/</guid>
      <description>A ball which is advanced from a pinned or stopped position on the five-man rod cannot be directly caught on the forward three-man rod of the same team regardless of whether or not the ball is touched by the opposing five-man rod.
23.1 A pinned ball is one that is pinned to the wall or playfield. A stopped ball is one that has completely stopped but has not been immediately advanced.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>22. Language and Behavior</title>
      <link>https://fooston.com/foosball-rules/language-and-behavior/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Sep 2017 21:41:09 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fooston.com/foosball-rules/language-and-behavior/</guid>
      <description>Unsportsmanlike conduct or comments made directly or indirectly by a player are not allowed. Violations of this rule may be grounds for a technical foul.
22.1 Calling the attention of the opposing team away from the game is not allowed (see Rule 20). Any shouts or sounds made during a match, even if of an enthusiastic nature, may be grounds for a technical foul.
22.2 Cursing by a player shall not be allowed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>21. Practice</title>
      <link>https://fooston.com/foosball-rules/practice/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Sep 2017 21:37:03 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fooston.com/foosball-rules/practice/</guid>
      <description>Practice shall be permitted on any table before the match begins and between games. Once a game has begun, practice shall not be permitted.
20.1 Practice is defined as moving the ball from one player figure to another or shooting the ball.
20.1.1 Illegal Practice is a judgment call by the Referee at the table. Inadvertent movement of the ball, or using the player figures to position the ball before the serve, does not constitute practice.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>20. Distraction</title>
      <link>https://fooston.com/foosball-rules/distraction/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Sep 2017 21:34:14 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fooston.com/foosball-rules/distraction/</guid>
      <description>Any movement or sound (including phones and electronic devices) made away from, or behind, the rod where the ball is in play may be judged as a distraction. It may be considered a distraction if the opponent taps the table top as a gesture of apology or approval during play. If a player believes he is being distracted, it is his responsibility to call for a Referee.
20.1 Banging the five-man rod or any rod prior to, during, or after a shot is considered a distraction.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>19. Alterations to the Table</title>
      <link>https://fooston.com/foosball-rules/alterations-to-the-table/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Sep 2017 21:16:33 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fooston.com/foosball-rules/alterations-to-the-table/</guid>
      <description>Playing area - no changes can be made that would affect the interior playing characteristics of the table by any player. This includes changes to the men, playing surface, bumpers, etc.
19.1 Players are not allowed to put sweat, spit, or any foreign substance on their hands to clean ball marks off the table. First offense is a warning and any subsequent violation is a Technical Foul.
19.1.1 Only manufacturer recommended cleaning agents or those supplied by the Tournament Organizer may be used to clean the surface.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>18. Reaching Into the Playing Area</title>
      <link>https://fooston.com/foosball-rules/reaching-into-the-playing-area/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Sep 2017 21:13:47 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fooston.com/foosball-rules/reaching-into-the-playing-area/</guid>
      <description>It is illegal for a player to reach into the play area while the ball is in play without first having permission from the opposing team or Referee whether he touches the ball or not. However, whenever the opposing team or Referee grants a player permission to reach into the playing area, it is legal for the player to do so.
18.1 A spinning ball is considered &amp;ldquo;in-play,&amp;rdquo; even if it is not in reach of a player figure.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>17. Reset</title>
      <link>https://fooston.com/foosball-rules/reset/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Sep 2017 21:01:23 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fooston.com/foosball-rules/reset/</guid>
      <description>If a defensive player bumps or shakes the table enough to impair the opponent’s ability to control the ball or execute a pass or shot, the Referee present will say “reset” and the time of possession plus number of times the ball struck the wall shall be reset. The player with the ball is not required to stop play so the defensive player should not relax or look up at the Referee when the call is made.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>16. Jarring</title>
      <link>https://fooston.com/foosball-rules/jarring/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Sep 2017 20:59:30 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fooston.com/foosball-rules/jarring/</guid>
      <description>Any banging of the side walls or movement of the table that causes the opponent to lose possession or prevents them from catching the ball is considered a jarring infraction. Simultaneous bumping of the wall, as part of a pass or shot, is not considered jarring unless there was excessive force that clearly prevented the opponent from gaining possession. Jars are accumulated for the entire match.
16.1 Any touching or contacting of the opponent&amp;rsquo;s rods that causes them to lose possession or prevents them from catching the ball will be considered a jarring infraction.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>15. Spinning the Rods</title>
      <link>https://fooston.com/foosball-rules/spinning-the-rods/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Sep 2017 20:57:37 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fooston.com/foosball-rules/spinning-the-rods/</guid>
      <description>Spinning of the rods is illegal. Spinning is defined as the rotation of any soccer figure more than 360 degrees before or more than 360° after striking the ball. In calculating the 360° you do not add the degrees spun prior to striking the ball to the degrees spun after striking the ball.
15.1 If a ball is advanced by an illegal spin the opposing team will have the option of continuing play from the current position or to serve the ball.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>14. Change of Positions</title>
      <link>https://fooston.com/foosball-rules/change-of-positions/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Sep 2017 20:52:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fooston.com/foosball-rules/change-of-positions/</guid>
      <description>In any doubles event, players may only play the two rods normally designated for his position. Once the ball is put into play, the players must play the same position until a point is scored, a team requests a time out, or a technical foul is called.
14.1 Either team may switch positions during a time out, between points, between games, or before and/or after a technical foul shot.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>13. Table Sides</title>
      <link>https://fooston.com/foosball-rules/table-sides/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Sep 2017 20:50:25 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fooston.com/foosball-rules/table-sides/</guid>
      <description>After each game is completed, teams have a 90 second time limit to begin the next game. If teams agree to switch sides of the table after the first game, they must continue to switch sides between games for the remainder of the match. If the teams decide not to switch sides after the first game, they must stay on the same sides for the remainder of the match.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>12. Point Scored</title>
      <link>https://fooston.com/foosball-rules/point-scored/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Sep 2017 20:48:57 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fooston.com/foosball-rules/point-scored/</guid>
      <description>A ball entering the goal shall count as a point, as long as it was legally scored. A ball which enters the goal but returns to the playing surface and/or leaves the table still counts as a goal.
12.1 If a point is not counted on the scoring markers and both teams agree that it was previously scored and inadvertently not marked up, the point shall count. If both teams do not agree that a point was scored and not marked up that point shall not be counted.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>11. Official Time Out</title>
      <link>https://fooston.com/foosball-rules/official-time-out/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Sep 2017 19:37:14 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fooston.com/foosball-rules/official-time-out/</guid>
      <description>An Official Time Out does not count towards the two time outs allowed per team per game. After an Official Time Out, the ball is put back into play as though a regular Time Out was called.
11.1 If a Referee is not present at the start of the match, and a dispute arises during play, either team may request a Referee. Such a request can be made at any point during the match that the ball is stopped or dead.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>10. Resuming Play After a Time Out</title>
      <link>https://fooston.com/foosball-rules/resuming-play-after-a-time-out/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Sep 2017 19:26:51 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fooston.com/foosball-rules/resuming-play-after-a-time-out/</guid>
      <description>Following a time out, the ball shall be put back into play at the rod of possession where the time out was called.
10.1 The Ready Protocol must be followed when resuming play following a time out. (See Rule 4.2)
10.1.1 As soon as the player in possession puts his hands back on the handles, if the ball leaves the current rod before the procedure of putting the ball back into play has begun, the opponent has the choice to continue play from the current position or to serve the ball.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>9. Time Out</title>
      <link>https://fooston.com/foosball-rules/time-out/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Sep 2017 19:16:43 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fooston.com/foosball-rules/time-out/</guid>
      <description>Each team is allowed two time outs per game during which the players may leave the table. Such time outs shall not exceed 30 seconds. If the ball is in play, time out may only be called by the team in possession of the ball. If the ball is not in play, either team may call time out.
9.1 Either team may take the full 30 seconds, even if the team that called the time out does not wish to take the full allotment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>8. Dead Ball</title>
      <link>https://fooston.com/foosball-rules/dead-ball/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Sep 2017 17:59:57 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fooston.com/foosball-rules/dead-ball/</guid>
      <description>A ball shall be declared a dead ball when it has completely stopped its motion and is not within reach of any player figure.
8.1 If the ball is declared dead anywhere between the five-man rods, it shall be put back into play at the five-man rod by the team who originally served the ball. (See Rule 4).
8.2 If the ball is declared dead between the goal and five-man rods, it shall be put back into play at the two-man rod nearest the spot of the dead ball.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>7. Ball Off the Table</title>
      <link>https://fooston.com/foosball-rules/ball-off-the-table/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Sep 2017 17:20:08 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fooston.com/foosball-rules/ball-off-the-table/</guid>
      <description>If the ball leaves the playing area and strikes the score markers, light fixture, or any object that is not part of the table, or if the ball rolls or comes to rest on the top of the cabinet, it shall be declared off the table. Otherwise, if the ball hits the top of the side rails or cabinet ends and subsequently returns to the playing surface, the ball is still in play.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>6. Ball in Play</title>
      <link>https://fooston.com/foosball-rules/ball-in-play/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Sep 2017 17:17:18 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fooston.com/foosball-rules/ball-in-play/</guid>
      <description>Once a ball is put into play it shall remain in play until the ball is hit off the table, a dead ball is declared, time out is called, or a point is scored.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>5. Subsequent Serves</title>
      <link>https://fooston.com/foosball-rules/subsequent-serves/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Sep 2017 17:15:32 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fooston.com/foosball-rules/subsequent-serves/</guid>
      <description>Following the first serve of a match, subsequent serves shall be made by the team last scored upon. The first serve in subsequent games of a multi-game match shall be made by the team that lost the preceding game.
5.1 If the ball is served by the wrong team, and the violation is discovered before the ball is scored, play shall be stopped and the ball shall be served by the proper team.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>4. Serve and Ready Protocol</title>
      <link>https://fooston.com/foosball-rules/serve-and-ready-protocol/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Sep 2017 16:57:57 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fooston.com/foosball-rules/serve-and-ready-protocol/</guid>
      <description>A serve is defined as putting the ball into play at the five-man rod at the beginning of a game, after a point is scored, or if the ball is awarded to a player on the five-man rod following a rules infraction. The ready protocol will be used whenever putting the ball into play.
4.1 The Serve. The serve shall begin with the ball stopped at the middle player figure of the five-man rod.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>3. To Start a Match</title>
      <link>https://fooston.com/foosball-rules/to-start-a-match/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Sep 2017 16:53:22 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fooston.com/foosball-rules/to-start-a-match/</guid>
      <description>Unless otherwise stated by the tournament director, a match shall consist of the first player or team to win 3 out of 5 games. Each game shall consist of 5 points. The final game of the match shall be to 5 points with a 2 point margin up to a maximum of 8 points.
3.1 The number of games played is the responsibility of the Tournament Director and will be published in the tournament announcement.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2. The Match</title>
      <link>https://fooston.com/foosball-rules/the-match/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Sep 2017 16:51:43 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fooston.com/foosball-rules/the-match/</guid>
      <description>Unless otherwise stated by the tournament director, a match shall consist of the first player or team to win 3 out of 5 games. Each game shall consist of 5 points. The final game of the match shall be to 5 points with a 2 point margin up to a maximum of 8 points.
2.1 The number of games played is the responsibility of the Tournament Director and will be published in the tournament announcement.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1. Code of Ethics</title>
      <link>https://fooston.com/foosball-rules/code-of-ethics/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Sep 2017 16:32:23 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fooston.com/foosball-rules/code-of-ethics/</guid>
      <description>Any action of an unsportsmanlike or unethical nature during tournament play, in the tournament room, or on the grounds of the host facility, will be considered a violation of the Code of Ethics. Mutual respect between all players, Referees and/or spectators is a requirement. It shall be the aim of every player and Referee to represent table-soccer in the most positive and sportsmanlike manner possible.
1.1 The penalty for breaking the Code of Ethics may be forfeiture of a game or match, expulsion from the tournament, and/or a fine.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Paralympic Regulations</title>
      <link>https://fooston.com/foosball-rules/paralympic-regulations/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Sep 2017 16:28:10 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fooston.com/foosball-rules/paralympic-regulations/</guid>
      <description>Eligibility  Players with congenital or acquired physical disabilities - A certificate of disability should be sent to the ITSF while getting the ITSF membership card, or at the time of registration for a match, in order to avoid problems during the match or after it. The ITSF Paralympic Commission will evaluate any exceptions to these regulations by analyzing each case individually.   Able-bodied players are not allowed to participate in competitions that are designated for disabled players, except during “Integrated sport” events where able and disabled players can play in doubles or for the same team.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Qualified Authorities</title>
      <link>https://fooston.com/foosball-rules/qualified-authorities/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Sep 2017 16:19:18 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fooston.com/foosball-rules/qualified-authorities/</guid>
      <description>This rulebook has been written and edited by the Rules Commission under the responsibility of the Sporting Commission. It is put to a vote and set up at the beginning of each season by the Executive Committee of the ITSF (International Table Soccer Federation). It can be examined and amended in a general assembly.   In cases of inconsistencies or of difficult situations, immediate amendments can be proposed by the Rules Commission in course of the season.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Introduction</title>
      <link>https://fooston.com/foosball-rules/introduction/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Sep 2017 00:20:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fooston.com/foosball-rules/introduction/</guid>
      <description>All Players and organizers must follow this rulebook.
 The rulebook is meant as a guide to assist the Referees. Its goal is above all to explain the rules of the game. And so, as much as the Referee’s goal is to show his authority for the good of the game, he must also be careful not to slow it down by a too strict arbitration.   Reminder: Federation Referees represent the highest authority of the rulebook in a tournament.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contents</title>
      <link>https://fooston.com/foosball-rules/contents/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Sep 2017 00:10:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fooston.com/foosball-rules/contents/</guid>
      <description>We&amp;rsquo;ve reproduced the official 2016 ITSF Rulebook.
 Forward Contents Introduction Qualified Authorities Materials and Hardware Paralympic Regulations   Code of Ethics The Match To Start a Match Serve and Ready Protocol Subsequent Serves Ball in Play Ball Off the Table Dead Ball Time Out Resuming Play After a Time Out Official Time Out Point Scored Table Sides Change of Positions Spinning the Rods Jarring Reset Reaching Into the Playing Area Alterations to the Table Distraction Practice Language and Behavior Passing Time of Possession Delay of Game Recalls and Forfeiture Technical Fouls Rules Decisions and Appeals Dress Code Tournament Director Side events  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Forward from the President of the ITSF Rules Commision</title>
      <link>https://fooston.com/foosball-rules/forward/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Sep 2017 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fooston.com/foosball-rules/forward/</guid>
      <description>This latest revision of the ITSF Rule Book is the culmination of a collaborative effort with input from many players and referees from around the world under the direction of the ITSF Rules Commission. Changes have been made to simplify some rules, to clarify others, and to make it easier for referees to officiate matches. Players are encouraged to learn and study these rules so that, regardless of one’s nationality or table preference, all may compete fairly according to the same standards of play.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Liberty Station</title>
      <link>https://fooston.com/weekly-tournaments/liberty-station/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Sep 2017 15:47:02 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fooston.com/weekly-tournaments/liberty-station/</guid>
      <description> Details  Mondays 8:00 PM: Get together for pickup games. The bar opens the tables for free play. Thursdays 8:30 PM: Typically a singles tournament but if too many players show up switches to doubles. Thursdays 10:00 PM: Doubles tournament.  ELO Ratings </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bubba&#39;s Sports Bar &amp; Grill</title>
      <link>https://fooston.com/weekly-tournaments/bubbas-sports-bar/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Sep 2017 11:54:48 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fooston.com/weekly-tournaments/bubbas-sports-bar/</guid>
      <description>Details  DYP - $10 per person Bubba&amp;rsquo;s adds $6 per head to the pot Signups start @ 8:45 PM 4 Tables Late sign ups (9pm or later) $15  Location Bubba&amp;rsquo;s Sports Bar &amp;amp; Grill 6225 Washington Ave., Houston, Texas 77007</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>0.25.1</title>
      <link>https://fooston.com/release-notes/0.25.1-relnotes/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Jul 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fooston.com/release-notes/0.25.1-relnotes/</guid>
      <description> This is a bug-fix release with a couple of important fixes.
Hugo now has:
 18277+ stars 456+ contributors 170+ themes  Fixes  Fix union when the first slice is empty dbbc5c48 @bep #3686 Navigate to changed on CREATE When working with content from IntelliJ IDE, like WebStorm, every file save is followed by two events: &amp;ldquo;RENAME&amp;rdquo; and then &amp;ldquo;CREATE&amp;rdquo;. 7bcc1ce6 @miltador Final (!) fix for issue with escaped JSON front matter 7f82b41a @bep #3682 Fix issue with escaped JSON front matter 84db6c74 @bep #3682  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>0.25</title>
      <link>https://fooston.com/release-notes/0.25-relnotes/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fooston.com/release-notes/0.25-relnotes/</guid>
      <description>Hugo 0.25 is the Kinder Surprise: It automatically opens the page you&amp;rsquo;re working on in the browser, it adds full AND and OR support in page queries, and you can now have templates per language.
If you start with hugo server --navigateToChanged, Hugo will navigate to the relevant page on save (see animated GIF). This is extremely useful for site-wide edits. Another very useful feature in this version is the added support for AND (intersect) and OR (union) filters when combined with where.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://fooston.com/readfiles/readme/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fooston.com/readfiles/readme/</guid>
      <description>readdirs Directory for Reusable Content Files in this directory are:
 Used in more than one place within the Hugo docs Used in Examples of readdir (i.e. in local file templates)  These files are called using the readfile shortcode (source).
You can call this shortcode in the docs as follows:
{{% readfile file=&amp;ldquo;/path/to/file.txt&amp;rdquo; markdown=&amp;ldquo;true&amp;rdquo; %}}
markdown=&amp;quot;true&amp;quot; is optional (default = &amp;quot;false&amp;quot;) and parses the string through the Blackfriday renderer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://fooston.com/readfiles/bfconfig/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fooston.com/readfiles/bfconfig/</guid>
      <description>Blackfriday Options  taskLists default: true
Blackfriday flag: Purpose: false turns off GitHub-style automatic task/TODO list generation. smartypants default: true Blackfriday flag: HTML_USE_SMARTYPANTS Purpose: false disables smart punctuation substitutions, including smart quotes, smart dashes, smart fractions, etc. If true, it may be fine-tuned with the angledQuotes, fractions, smartDashes, and latexDashes flags (see below). smartypantsQuotesNBSP default: false Blackfriday flag: HTML_SMARTYPANTS_QUOTES_NBSP Purpose: true enables French style Guillemets with non-breaking space inside the quotes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://fooston.com/readfiles/dateformatting/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fooston.com/readfiles/dateformatting/</guid>
      <description>Go templates format your dates according to a single reference time:
Mon Jan 2 15:04:05 MST 2006  You can think of MST as 07, thus making the reference format string a sequence of numbers. The following is taken directly from the Go docs:
Jan 2 15:04:05 2006 MST 1 2 3 4 5 6 -7  Hugo Date Templating Reference Each of the following examples show the reference formatting string followed by the string Hugo will output in your HTML.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://fooston.com/readfiles/menuvars/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fooston.com/readfiles/menuvars/</guid>
      <description> .URL string .Name string .Menu string .Identifier string .Pre template.HTML .Post template.HTML .Weight int .Parent string .Children Menu  Note that menus also have the following functions available as well:
 .HasChildren boolean  Additionally, there are some relevant functions available to menus on a page:
 .IsMenuCurrent (menu string, menuEntry *MenuEntry ) boolean .HasMenuCurrent (menu string, menuEntry *MenuEntry) boolean  </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>