<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Foosball in Houston, TX on Fooston</title>
    <link>https://fooston.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Foosball in Houston, TX on Fooston</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2017 12:00:00 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://fooston.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>2016 Rule Book</title>
      <link>https://fooston.com/rules/2016-rule-book/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Sep 2017 00:55:56 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fooston.com/rules/2016-rule-book/</guid>
      <description>www.tablesocer.org
Foreword from the President of the ITSF Rules Commission This latest revision of the ITSF Rule Book is the culmination of a collaborative effort with input from many players and referees from around the world under the direction of the ITSF Rules Commission. Changes have been made to simplify some rules, to clarify others, and to make it easier for referees to officiate matches. Players are encouraged to learn and study these rules so that, regardless of one’s nationality or table preference, all may compete fairly according to the same standards of play.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Liberty Station</title>
      <link>https://fooston.com/tournaments/liberty-station/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Sep 2017 15:47:02 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fooston.com/tournaments/liberty-station/</guid>
      <description> Details  Mondays 8:00 PM: Get together for pickup games. The bar opens the tables for free play. Thursdays 8:30 PM: Typically a singles tournament but if too many players show up switches to doubles. Thursdays 10:00 PM: Doubles tournament.  ELO Ratings </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bubba&#39;s Sports Bar &amp; Grill</title>
      <link>https://fooston.com/tournaments/bubbas-sports-bar/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Sep 2017 11:54:48 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fooston.com/tournaments/bubbas-sports-bar/</guid>
      <description>Details  $10 per person DYP begins at 8:30pm Late Sign Ups (9pm or later) $15  Location Bubba&amp;rsquo;s Sports Bar &amp;amp; Grill 6225 Washington Ave., Houston, Texas 77007</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>0.25.1</title>
      <link>https://fooston.com/release-notes/0.25.1-relnotes/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Jul 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fooston.com/release-notes/0.25.1-relnotes/</guid>
      <description> This is a bug-fix release with a couple of important fixes.
Hugo now has:
 18277+ stars 456+ contributors 170+ themes  Fixes  Fix union when the first slice is empty dbbc5c48 @bep #3686 Navigate to changed on CREATE When working with content from IntelliJ IDE, like WebStorm, every file save is followed by two events: &amp;ldquo;RENAME&amp;rdquo; and then &amp;ldquo;CREATE&amp;rdquo;. 7bcc1ce6 @miltador Final (!) fix for issue with escaped JSON front matter 7f82b41a @bep #3682 Fix issue with escaped JSON front matter 84db6c74 @bep #3682  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>0.25</title>
      <link>https://fooston.com/release-notes/0.25-relnotes/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fooston.com/release-notes/0.25-relnotes/</guid>
      <description>Hugo 0.25 is the Kinder Surprise: It automatically opens the page you&amp;rsquo;re working on in the browser, it adds full AND and OR support in page queries, and you can now have templates per language.
If you start with hugo server --navigateToChanged, Hugo will navigate to the relevant page on save (see animated GIF). This is extremely useful for site-wide edits. Another very useful feature in this version is the added support for AND (intersect) and OR (union) filters when combined with where.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://fooston.com/readfiles/readme/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fooston.com/readfiles/readme/</guid>
      <description>readdirs Directory for Reusable Content Files in this directory are:
 Used in more than one place within the Hugo docs Used in Examples of readdir (i.e. in local file templates)  These files are called using the readfile shortcode (source).
You can call this shortcode in the docs as follows:
{{% readfile file=&amp;ldquo;/path/to/file.txt&amp;rdquo; markdown=&amp;ldquo;true&amp;rdquo; %}}
markdown=&amp;quot;true&amp;quot; is optional (default = &amp;quot;false&amp;quot;) and parses the string through the Blackfriday renderer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://fooston.com/readfiles/bfconfig/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fooston.com/readfiles/bfconfig/</guid>
      <description>Blackfriday Options  taskLists default: true
Blackfriday flag: Purpose: false turns off GitHub-style automatic task/TODO list generation. smartypants default: true Blackfriday flag: HTML_USE_SMARTYPANTS Purpose: false disables smart punctuation substitutions, including smart quotes, smart dashes, smart fractions, etc. If true, it may be fine-tuned with the angledQuotes, fractions, smartDashes, and latexDashes flags (see below). smartypantsQuotesNBSP default: false Blackfriday flag: HTML_SMARTYPANTS_QUOTES_NBSP Purpose: true enables French style Guillemets with non-breaking space inside the quotes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://fooston.com/readfiles/dateformatting/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fooston.com/readfiles/dateformatting/</guid>
      <description>Go templates format your dates according to a single reference time:
Mon Jan 2 15:04:05 MST 2006  You can think of MST as 07, thus making the reference format string a sequence of numbers. The following is taken directly from the Go docs:
Jan 2 15:04:05 2006 MST 1 2 3 4 5 6 -7  Hugo Date Templating Reference Each of the following examples show the reference formatting string followed by the string Hugo will output in your HTML.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://fooston.com/readfiles/menuvars/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fooston.com/readfiles/menuvars/</guid>
      <description> .URL string .Name string .Menu string .Identifier string .Pre template.HTML .Post template.HTML .Weight int .Parent string .Children Menu  Note that menus also have the following functions available as well:
 .HasChildren boolean  Additionally, there are some relevant functions available to menus on a page:
 .IsMenuCurrent (menu string, menuEntry *MenuEntry ) boolean .HasMenuCurrent (menu string, menuEntry *MenuEntry) boolean  </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>