<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Foosball in Houston, TX on Fooston</title>
    <link>https://fooston.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Foosball in Houston, TX on Fooston</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2017 12:00:00 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://fooston.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>7. Ball Off the Table</title>
      <link>https://fooston.com/rules/ball-off-the-table/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Sep 2017 17:20:08 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fooston.com/rules/ball-off-the-table/</guid>
      <description>If the ball leaves the playing area and strikes the score markers, light fixture, or any object that is not part of the table, or if the ball rolls or comes to rest on the top of the cabinet, it shall be declared off the table. Otherwise, if the ball hits the top of the side rails or cabinet ends and subsequently returns to the playing surface, the ball is still in play.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>6. Ball in Play</title>
      <link>https://fooston.com/rules/ball-in-play/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Sep 2017 17:17:18 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fooston.com/rules/ball-in-play/</guid>
      <description>Once a ball is put into play it shall remain in play until the ball is hit off the table, a dead ball is declared, time out is called, or a point is scored.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>5. Subsequent Serves</title>
      <link>https://fooston.com/rules/subsequent-serves/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Sep 2017 17:15:32 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fooston.com/rules/subsequent-serves/</guid>
      <description>Following the first serve of a match, subsequent serves shall be made by the team last scored upon. The first serve in subsequent games of a multi-game match shall be made by the team that lost the preceding game.
5.1 If the ball is served by the wrong team, and the violation is discovered before the ball is scored, play shall be stopped and the ball shall be served by the proper team.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>4. Serve and Ready Protocol</title>
      <link>https://fooston.com/rules/serve-and-ready-protocol/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Sep 2017 16:57:57 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fooston.com/rules/serve-and-ready-protocol/</guid>
      <description>A serve is defined as putting the ball into play at the five-man rod at the beginning of a game, after a point is scored, or if the ball is awarded to a player on the five-man rod following a rules infraction. The ready protocol will be used whenever putting the ball into play.
4.1 The Serve. The serve shall begin with the ball stopped at the middle player figure of the five-man rod.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>3. To Start a Match</title>
      <link>https://fooston.com/rules/to-start-a-match/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Sep 2017 16:53:22 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fooston.com/rules/to-start-a-match/</guid>
      <description>Unless otherwise stated by the tournament director, a match shall consist of the first player or team to win 3 out of 5 games. Each game shall consist of 5 points. The final game of the match shall be to 5 points with a 2 point margin up to a maximum of 8 points.
3.1 The number of games played is the responsibility of the Tournament Director and will be published in the tournament announcement.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2. The Match</title>
      <link>https://fooston.com/rules/the-match/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Sep 2017 16:51:43 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fooston.com/rules/the-match/</guid>
      <description>Unless otherwise stated by the tournament director, a match shall consist of the first player or team to win 3 out of 5 games. Each game shall consist of 5 points. The final game of the match shall be to 5 points with a 2 point margin up to a maximum of 8 points.
2.1 The number of games played is the responsibility of the Tournament Director and will be published in the tournament announcement.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1. Code of Ethics</title>
      <link>https://fooston.com/rules/code-of-ethics/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Sep 2017 16:32:23 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fooston.com/rules/code-of-ethics/</guid>
      <description>Any action of an unsportsmanlike or unethical nature during tournament play, in the tournament room, or on the grounds of the host facility, will be considered a violation of the Code of Ethics. Mutual respect between all players, Referees and/or spectators is a requirement. It shall be the aim of every player and Referee to represent table-soccer in the most positive and sportsmanlike manner possible.
1.1 The penalty for breaking the Code of Ethics may be forfeiture of a game or match, expulsion from the tournament, and/or a fine.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Paralympic Regulations</title>
      <link>https://fooston.com/rules/paralympic-regulations/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Sep 2017 16:28:10 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fooston.com/rules/paralympic-regulations/</guid>
      <description>Eligibility  Players with congenital or acquired physical disabilities - A certificate of disability should be sent to the ITSF while getting the ITSF membership card, or at the time of registration for a match, in order to avoid problems during the match or after it. The ITSF Paralympic Commission will evaluate any exceptions to these regulations by analyzing each case individually.   Able-bodied players are not allowed to participate in competitions that are designated for disabled players, except during “Integrated sport” events where able and disabled players can play in doubles or for the same team.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Materials and Hardware</title>
      <link>https://fooston.com/rules/materials-and-hardware/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Sep 2017 16:22:04 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fooston.com/rules/materials-and-hardware/</guid>
      <description>Table  The Official tables are voted by ITSF General Assembly. This choice of table can be modified according to the agreements between the ITSF and manufacturers and partners.   The organizers must provide competitive equipment (sandpapered players, clean and straight bars).   In no cases may the surface of the table be sandpapered, and doing so will be penalized by exclusion of the tournament and reimbursement of the surface.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Qualified Authorities</title>
      <link>https://fooston.com/rules/qualified-authorities/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Sep 2017 16:19:18 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fooston.com/rules/qualified-authorities/</guid>
      <description>This rulebook has been written and edited by the Rules Commission under the responsibility of the Sporting Commission. It is put to a vote and set up at the beginning of each season by the Executive Committee of the ITSF (International Table Soccer Federation). It can be examined and amended in a general assembly.   In cases of inconsistencies or of difficult situations, immediate amendments can be proposed by the Rules Commission in course of the season.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Introduction</title>
      <link>https://fooston.com/rules/introduction/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Sep 2017 16:18:12 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fooston.com/rules/introduction/</guid>
      <description>All Players and organizers must follow this rulebook.
 The rulebook is meant as a guide to assist the Referees. Its goal is above all to explain the rules of the game. And so, as much as the Referee’s goal is to show his authority for the good of the game, he must also be careful not to slow it down by a too strict arbitration.   Reminder: Federation Referees represent the highest authority of the rulebook in a tournament.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contents</title>
      <link>https://fooston.com/rules/contents/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Sep 2017 16:15:30 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fooston.com/rules/contents/</guid>
      <description>CONTENTS INTRODUCTION QUALIFIED AUTHORITIES MATERIALS AND HARDWARE PARALYMPIC REGULATIONS 1. Code of Ethics 2. The Match 3. To Start a Match 4. Serve and Ready Protocol 5. Subsequent Serves 6. Ball in Play 7. Ball Off the Table 8. Dead Ball 9. Time Out 10. Resuming Play After a Time Out 11. Official Time Out 12. Point Scored 13. Table Sides 14. Change of Positions 15. Spinning the Rods 16.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Forward from the President of the ITSF Rules Commision</title>
      <link>https://fooston.com/rules/forward/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Sep 2017 16:10:54 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fooston.com/rules/forward/</guid>
      <description>This latest revision of the ITSF Rule Book is the culmination of a collaborative effort with input from many players and referees from around the world under the direction of the ITSF Rules Commission. Changes have been made to simplify some rules, to clarify others, and to make it easier for referees to officiate matches. Players are encouraged to learn and study these rules so that, regardless of one’s nationality or table preference, all may compete fairly according to the same standards of play.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2016 Rule Book</title>
      <link>https://fooston.com/rules/2016-rule-book/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Sep 2017 00:55:56 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fooston.com/rules/2016-rule-book/</guid>
      <description>www.tablesocer.org
Foreword from the President of the ITSF Rules Commission This latest revision of the ITSF Rule Book is the culmination of a collaborative effort with input from many players and referees from around the world under the direction of the ITSF Rules Commission. Changes have been made to simplify some rules, to clarify others, and to make it easier for referees to officiate matches. Players are encouraged to learn and study these rules so that, regardless of one’s nationality or table preference, all may compete fairly according to the same standards of play.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Liberty Station</title>
      <link>https://fooston.com/tournaments/liberty-station/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Sep 2017 15:47:02 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fooston.com/tournaments/liberty-station/</guid>
      <description> Details  Mondays 8:00 PM: Get together for pickup games. The bar opens the tables for free play. Thursdays 8:30 PM: Typically a singles tournament but if too many players show up switches to doubles. Thursdays 10:00 PM: Doubles tournament.  ELO Ratings </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bubba&#39;s Sports Bar &amp; Grill</title>
      <link>https://fooston.com/tournaments/bubbas-sports-bar/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Sep 2017 11:54:48 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fooston.com/tournaments/bubbas-sports-bar/</guid>
      <description>Details  $10 per person DYP begins at 8:30pm Late Sign Ups (9pm or later) $15  Location Bubba&amp;rsquo;s Sports Bar &amp;amp; Grill 6225 Washington Ave., Houston, Texas 77007</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>0.25.1</title>
      <link>https://fooston.com/release-notes/0.25.1-relnotes/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Jul 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fooston.com/release-notes/0.25.1-relnotes/</guid>
      <description> This is a bug-fix release with a couple of important fixes.
Hugo now has:
 18277+ stars 456+ contributors 170+ themes  Fixes  Fix union when the first slice is empty dbbc5c48 @bep #3686 Navigate to changed on CREATE When working with content from IntelliJ IDE, like WebStorm, every file save is followed by two events: &amp;ldquo;RENAME&amp;rdquo; and then &amp;ldquo;CREATE&amp;rdquo;. 7bcc1ce6 @miltador Final (!) fix for issue with escaped JSON front matter 7f82b41a @bep #3682 Fix issue with escaped JSON front matter 84db6c74 @bep #3682  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>0.25</title>
      <link>https://fooston.com/release-notes/0.25-relnotes/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fooston.com/release-notes/0.25-relnotes/</guid>
      <description>Hugo 0.25 is the Kinder Surprise: It automatically opens the page you&amp;rsquo;re working on in the browser, it adds full AND and OR support in page queries, and you can now have templates per language.
If you start with hugo server --navigateToChanged, Hugo will navigate to the relevant page on save (see animated GIF). This is extremely useful for site-wide edits. Another very useful feature in this version is the added support for AND (intersect) and OR (union) filters when combined with where.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://fooston.com/readfiles/readme/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fooston.com/readfiles/readme/</guid>
      <description>readdirs Directory for Reusable Content Files in this directory are:
 Used in more than one place within the Hugo docs Used in Examples of readdir (i.e. in local file templates)  These files are called using the readfile shortcode (source).
You can call this shortcode in the docs as follows:
{{% readfile file=&amp;ldquo;/path/to/file.txt&amp;rdquo; markdown=&amp;ldquo;true&amp;rdquo; %}}
markdown=&amp;quot;true&amp;quot; is optional (default = &amp;quot;false&amp;quot;) and parses the string through the Blackfriday renderer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://fooston.com/readfiles/bfconfig/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fooston.com/readfiles/bfconfig/</guid>
      <description>Blackfriday Options  taskLists default: true
Blackfriday flag: Purpose: false turns off GitHub-style automatic task/TODO list generation. smartypants default: true Blackfriday flag: HTML_USE_SMARTYPANTS Purpose: false disables smart punctuation substitutions, including smart quotes, smart dashes, smart fractions, etc. If true, it may be fine-tuned with the angledQuotes, fractions, smartDashes, and latexDashes flags (see below). smartypantsQuotesNBSP default: false Blackfriday flag: HTML_SMARTYPANTS_QUOTES_NBSP Purpose: true enables French style Guillemets with non-breaking space inside the quotes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://fooston.com/readfiles/dateformatting/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fooston.com/readfiles/dateformatting/</guid>
      <description>Go templates format your dates according to a single reference time:
Mon Jan 2 15:04:05 MST 2006  You can think of MST as 07, thus making the reference format string a sequence of numbers. The following is taken directly from the Go docs:
Jan 2 15:04:05 2006 MST 1 2 3 4 5 6 -7  Hugo Date Templating Reference Each of the following examples show the reference formatting string followed by the string Hugo will output in your HTML.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://fooston.com/readfiles/menuvars/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fooston.com/readfiles/menuvars/</guid>
      <description> .URL string .Name string .Menu string .Identifier string .Pre template.HTML .Post template.HTML .Weight int .Parent string .Children Menu  Note that menus also have the following functions available as well:
 .HasChildren boolean  Additionally, there are some relevant functions available to menus on a page:
 .IsMenuCurrent (menu string, menuEntry *MenuEntry ) boolean .HasMenuCurrent (menu string, menuEntry *MenuEntry) boolean  </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>